submiturlhere.com 2008-09-29

# Privacy Policy

**Submiturlhere.com Privacy Policy.**

## Information Automatically Logged

The only information we collect from a normal web site visit is the name of your internet service provider, the browser and type of machine you are using, the web site that referred you to us, the pages you request and the date and time you request them. We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of the site to our visitors.

## Personal Information

Submiturlhere.com operates a web directory and if you request to submit your site, we collect contact information which is used to review your site for inclusion in our directory or to contact you if there is a need for a revision to your site.

All information is used for communication purposes only with you and is not provided to any third party

Submiturlhere.com does not sell or otherwise disclose user information. This policy has no exceptions. We do not sell or exchange your information with any other organization, public, private, or non-profit.

## External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Submiturlhere.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Contacting Submiturlhere.com

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us by sending an email to admin -@- submiturlhere.com or by filling the contact form.

This privacy policy is subject to change and we advise you to review it periodically
